Toggle navigation

* Search  
    
* Awards

    **Introducing Instruct Counsel**
    
    The next generation search tool for finding the right lawyer for you.
    
* More

* Resources

* Research tools

* Resources
* Research tools
* Who's Who Legal

* Learn

Analytics
---------

Review your content's performance and reach.

Content Development
-------------------

Become your target audience’s go-to resource for today’s hottest topics.

Client Intelligence
-------------------

Understand your clients’ strategies and the most pressing issues they are facing.

Competitor Intelligence
-----------------------

Keep a step ahead of your key competitors and benchmark against them.

Privacy Policy
==============

We are Law Business Research. We’re a UK company, registered number 03281866, and our registered office is Holborn Gate, 330 High Holborn, WC1V 7QT, London, United Kingdom.

We operate the Lexology website and subscription service. This statement explains what we do with your personal information when you register to use that website, subscribe to use our service, and how to exercise your rights over it.

If you have any questions about our use of your personal information, or if you want to exercise your rights, you can contact our data privacy team. The best way to do this is by email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.lexology.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), but if you prefer you can also write to us at: Data Protection Team, Law Business Research, Holborn Gate, 330 High Holborn, WC1V 7QT, London, United Kingdom.

**Who is in charge of your information**

In respect of the personal information you give us when you subscribe to Lexology or register to use the Lexology website, we are the “data controller” responsible for that information.

**The information we may collect about you**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

* **Information you give us.** You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site www.lexology.com or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise.
    * This includes information you provide when you register to use our site, subscribe to our service, sign up for newsletters, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our site and when you report a problem with our site.
    * The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, personal description and photograph, educational and employment history.

* **Information we collect about you.** With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information:
    * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
    * information about your visit or visits from your IP address, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

* **Information we receive from other sources.**
    * We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them;
    * We may receive information about you from your employer where you access services under a corporate subscription.
    * We may collect your personal details from other sources including where emails are forwarded to you or where we receive your contact details in an automatic out of office response to an email sent by us.

**Uses Made of the Information**

We use information held about you in the following ways**:**

* to tailor the content that we display to you;
* to deliver the service and to correspond with you in relation to the product;
* to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already used;
* to notify you about changes to our service;
* to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other device used to access our site.
* for system administration and to report aggregated statistical information about browsing patterns and actions which does not identify any individual;
* to store usage logs which may be used by us to provide existing and potential authors, contributors, associations we partner with, subscribers and clients with firm-level (ie not individual) information about the user base and usage patterns;
* to administer our site and for internal operations, including product development, troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
* to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
* to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
* as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
* to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.
* we may combine information received from other sources with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above.

**Disclosure of your information**

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We will not usually share your personal information with other third parties without your consent but may do so in the following situations:

* If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of LBR, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction;
* where we share aggregated information, which does not identify individuals with potential authors, contributors, subscribers and clients;
* where we are requested to provide information by authorised third parties or regulatory or governmental agencies investigating illegal activities;
* where we believe that an emergency, illegal activity or some other reasonable basis exists for notifying the relevant authority;
* where we use sub-contractors to provide the service. Any such sub-contractor will only use your personal information for the purposes of providing services to us and will have no right to use your personal information for its own purposes;
* In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
* If LBR or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
* Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. Save as expressly stated, we do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users. We may also use such  
    aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
* We may hold events including seminars and conferences which are sponsored by third parties or have third party speakers. Where you register for one of these events we may share your details with those third parties.
* Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site.
* We use third party payment processing services when you make payment through our site. We do not have access to any credit card or other financial information processed by the third party.

**Where we store your personal data**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, hosting or maintaining our websites, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**The legal basis on which we deal with your personal information**

Under the new data protection law starting in May 2018 we have a number of lawful reasons that we can use (or 'process') your personal information. One of the lawful reasons is called 'legitimate interests'.

Broadly speaking Legitimate Interests means that we can process your personal information if:

•           We have a genuine and legitimate reason and we are not harming any of your rights and interests

So, what does this mean? When you provide your personal details to us we use your information for our legitimate business interests to send you marketing communications or to gather information about how you use our website. Before doing this, though, we will also carefully consider and balance any potential impact on you and your rights.

Some other typical examples of when we might use the approach are for preventing fraud, maintaining the security of our system, data analytics, enhancing, modifying or improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our campaigns.

When we use your personal information in order to create or maintain your Lexology subscription or your access to the Lexology website, we do this on the basis that it is necessary for us to do so in order to perform the contract we are entering into with you to provide you with your Lexology subscription or your Lexology website access.

**Cookies**

If Lexology’s website is to work properly, you will need to ensure that your web browser is set to accept cookies. A cookie is a small file (or record in a file) which the website can send to your browser which may then store it on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow LBR to analyse web traffic and to determine more popular areas of its website. Cookies also allow LBR to make its website more user friendly by allowing LBR to save all registration and subscription details or passwords so that you do not have to re-enter every time you visit the Lexology website.  The cookie will stay on your computer and will only be used should you enter the Lexology website. Notwithstanding the above, you do not have to accept cookies and you should read the information that came with your web browser software to see how you can set up your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and to give you the opportunity to decide to accept or reject it. Our cookies will not transmit any information to us about you other than concerning your use of the Lexology website. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them, see our [cookie](https://www.lexology.com/Cookies) policy.

**Keeping your information up to date, and how long we will keep your information for**

It is your responsibility to ensure that the information you submit when subscribing for Lexology is complete, accurate and up to date and it is your responsibility to notify us if that information changes.

We will keep the information that you provide us when you visit the Lexology website for a period of 3 years, after which it will be deleted.  
  
We will keep the information that you provide us when you subscribe, to Lexology for as long as you continue to be a subscriber, for 3 years after you have ceased to be a subscriber, and for 3 years after you last log into your Lexology account (but are not a full Lexology subscriber), after which it will be deleted.

We will keep the information that you provide us when registering for a Lexology webinar for a period of 3 years, after which it will be deleted.

**Your rights and how to exercise them**

The law gives you certain rights in respect of the information that we hold about you. Below is a short overview of the most commonly-used rights. It is not a complete, exhaustive statement of your rights in respect of your personal data.

The website of the Information Commissioner’s Office ([https://ico.org.uk/](https://ico.org.uk/)) has a wealth of useful information in respect of your rights over your personal data.

If you wish to exercise your rights, the best way to do so is by email to the office of our data protection officer at [\[email protected\]](https://www.lexology.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), but if you prefer you can also write to us at the address above.

**Your right to unsubscribe**

When you receive marketing communications from us you have the right to unsubscribe at any time. You can do that by following the unsubscribe link in the email, or by contacting us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.lexology.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If you unsubscribe, we will stop sending you marketing communications.

**Your right to a copy of the information we hold about you**

With some exceptions designed to protect the rights of others, you have the right to a copy of the personal data that we hold about you, as well as information about what we do with it, who we share it with and how long we will hold it for. We may make a reasonable charge for additional copies of that data beyond the first copy, based on our administrative costs.

**Your right to have inaccurate information about you corrected**

You have the right to have the information we hold about you corrected if it is factually inaccurate. In most cases the easiest way to do that is to contact us and let us know what information needs to be changed.

**Your right to have your information deleted in some circumstances**

In some circumstances, you have the right to require us to delete the information that we hold about you. In particular, if you cease being an Lexology subscriber and we no longer need to process your personal data, then we will delete the relevant data from our systems.

**Your right to complain to the ICO**

You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our handling of your personal information with the Information Commissioner’s Office. You can contact them on 0303 123 1113.

Resources

Who's Who Legal

More

Legal

Contact

* [\[email protected\]](https://www.lexology.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Search
